Fried, John H. E.; Papers ger014
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Writings of John H. E. Fried, 1931-1990; 10
  - Speeches, 1931-1989; 10.2; 113 file folders
    - "International Promotion of Human Rights by Non-Governmental Organizations (NGOs)". American Political Science Association meeting, Los Angeles, 1970 September 11; Typescripts, program (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 4)
    - "Achievements and Problems of the United Nations Security Council". Symposium on 25 Years of the United Nations, Louisiana State University, New Orleans, 1970 October; Typescripts (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 5)
    - "Observations on the United States Invasion of Cambodia". Oslo, 1971 June 20-1971 June 25; Mimeographed typescripts (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 6)
    - "Anniversary of the Nurnberg Judgment: Oct. 1946-Oct. 1971". Lehmann College, 1971 October; Typescript (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 7)
    - "L'utilisation de Pays neutres par les Etats-Unis comme 'Sanctuaires' pour leur guerre d'Indochine, et l'invasion du Cambodge". Algiers, 1971 November 26-1971 November 28; Mimeographed typescripts (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 8)
    - "Use of Neural Countries by the U.S.A. as 'Sanctuaries' for Its Indochina War, and the Invasion of Cambodia". Algiers, 1971 November 26-1971 November 28; Mimeo (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 9)
      English version.
    - "The Dichotomy Between Morality and National Interest". Conference on Morality Among Nations, Plattsburgh, NY, 1972 February 22-1972 February 24; Typescripts (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 10)
    - "Transnational Control in the Area of Criminal Justice". American Society of International Law, 1972 April 29; Reprint, typescript (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 11)
    - "Why Are We Still in Indochina?" Lehmann College Notes, 1972 May 04 (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 12)
    - "Independent Recognition and United Nations Membership of Two Germanies". United Nations Church Center, NY, 1972 June 02-1972 June 03; Typescript, correspondence (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 13)
    - "War by Ecocide". International Commission of Enquiry into U.S. Crimes in Indochina, Stockholm, 1972 June 02-1972 June 04; Mimeographed text (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 14)
    - "Objectives, Personnel, Public Information and Financing in the UN System". Ohio State University, 1973 March 16; Program, correspondence (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 15)
    - "International Adjudication of International Criminality". World Peace Through Law Conference, Abidjan, Ivory Coast, 1973 August; Typescripts (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 16)
    - "Arab Israel Conflict After UN Cease Fire". Lehmann College, 1973 October 24; Notes (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 17)
    - "Will the 1973 Paris Agreement on Vietnam Hold?" Lehmann College, 1974 February 27; Notes (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 18)
    - "Differences between the Nuremberg Tribunal of 1945/6 and the Proposed International Criminal Court". Brussels, 1974 May 20-1974 May 22; Typescript (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 19)
    - "The President's Powers to Take the U.S. into War". Lehmann College, 1975 March 19; Advertisements (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 20)
    - Lecture to Italian Students Club, 1975 November; Notes (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 21)
    - "Continuing Significance of the Nuremberg Principles". Helsinki, 1976 September 24; Typescript, notes (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 22)
    - "Thirty Years after Nuremberg". Lehmann College, 1976 October 20-1976 October 21; Notes, clipping (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 23)
    - "The Policy of Secret Disappearance in Chile in the Light of Nuremberg Precedents". Bonn, 1976 November 24-1976 November 26; Typescripts, clippings, correspondence (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 24)
    - "Verbrechen gegen die Menschlichkeit der chilenischen Junta im Lichte der Nürnberger Prozesse". Nuremberg, 1976 November 26; Typescript (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 25)
    - "La Signification permanente des principes de Nuremberg". Paris, 1976 December 11; Typescripts, notes (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 26)
    - "Crimes of the Chilean Junta". Community Church of New York, 1977 January 22; Advertisement, correspondence (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 27)
    - Remarks. Lehmann College, 1977 May 05; Typescript (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 28)
    - "Removing Some Major Obstacles to Disarmament and Détente". World Peace Council, Helsinki, 1977 Summer; Typescripts, notes (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 29)
    - "The Conspiracy Charge at the Nuremberg Trial against the Major German War Criminals". Hofstra University, 1977 November 03; Typed notes (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 30)
    - "Growing Dangers Require a Broadened Approach by the Peace Movement. Manhattan College, 1977 November 11-1977 November 12; Typed notes, correspondence (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 31)
    - "Removing Some Major Obstacles to Disarmament and Détente". World Conference on Disarmament and Détente, Washington, D.C., 1978 January 25-1978 January 26; Typed notes (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 32)
    - "Disarmament and the UN System". Church Center, NY, 1978 June 05; Advertisement, typed notes (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 33)
    - Ninth World Congress of Sociology, Uppsala, Sweden, 1978 August 14-1978 August 19; Typed notes, correspondence (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 34)
    - "The Nuremberg Trial: Reminiscences by a Participant". Network Canada Conference, 1978 December 28-1979 January 01; Program, correspondence (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 35)
    - "The Positive Messages of 'Nuremberg' for the Nuclear Age". IPSA World Congress, Moscow, 1979 August 17; Typescripts, notes (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 36)
    - "30th DDR Anniversary". International Conference on the Reality of the German Democratic Republic, Columbia University, 1979 December 07; Typed notes, clipping (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 37)
    - "Nuclear Weapons: Current U.S. Policy - Law of Warfare". Wayne State University, 1980 March 20; Advertisement, notes (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 38)
    - "The Escallating Danger: from Deterrence Doctrine to First Strike, or Counterforce Doctrine". Dundas, Ottowa, 1980 June 19; Program, clippings, notes (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 39)
    - "Remarks on the Representation of Kampuchea at the 35th Session of the General Assembly". UN Church Center, 1980 September 15; Typescript, clippings (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 40)
    - "The Law Absolutely Prohibits Any First Nuclear Attack". International Association of Democratic Lawyers, Malta, 1980 November 13-1980 November 17; Typescript, programs (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 41)
    - "Erstgebrauch Nuklearer Waffen ist voelkerrechtlich verboten". Hamburg, 1981 April 24; Typescripts (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 42)
    - Speech at UN Church Center, 1981 June 05; Typescript (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 43)
    - "New International Economy". Center for Cuban Studies, NY, 1982 March 25; Typed note cards (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 44)
    - Speech on Nuclear War. Church of Heavenly Rest, 1982 June 27; Typescript (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 45)
    - "Would a First Use of Nuclear Weapons be Permissible under Existing International Law?" Rio de Janeiro, 1982 August 09-1982 August 14; Typescripts (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 46)
    - "On the Illegality of Nuclear Weapons". SUNY at Stony Brook, 1982 October 12; Typescript (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 47)
    - "Remarks on the Global Ramifications of the Israel-Lebanon War". Brussels, 1982 October 23; Typescript, conference materials (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 48)
    - "Appeal to the People of the U.S." International Conference of Lawyers, Algiers, 1982 December 10-1982 December 12; Typescript, correspondence (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 49)
    - "The Preparations for Nuclear War in the Light of International Law". Nuremberg, 1983 February 18; Typescript, conference materials (Box 16 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 50)
    - "Illegality of first use of nuclear weapons". Colorado State University, 1983 April 29; Notes, correspondence, clipping (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 1)
    - "Beliefs That May Destroy Us: Arguments for Nuclear Weapons". University of Denver School of Law, 1983 May 02; Typescript (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 2)
    - "Les Membres de l'Otan n'ont pas d'obligation de participer à la guerre nucleaire". Brussels, 1983 October 01-1983 October 02; Typescript, notes, conference materials (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 3)
    - Stockholm International Peace Research Institute, 1983 October; Typescripts (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 4)
    - "Nazi War Criminals and International Law". Conference of Holocaust Survivors in Pursuit of Justice. Temple Israel, Albany, NY, 1984 April 27; Typescript, conference materials (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 5)
    - "Code of Conduct for Nuclear Weapon States". International Association of Democratic Lawyers, Athens, 1984 October 18; Typescript, conference materials (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 6)
    - "The Axioms Underlying the Nuclear Arms Race: The More Destruction, the Better; and the Less Reflection, the Better." International Forum for Peace and Security in Europe, Brussels, 1985 February 28-1985 March 03; Typescript, conference materials (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 7)
    - "Nuremberg Medical Ethical Code". Haifa University School of Medicine, 1985 July 05; Typed notes, materials (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 8)
    - "The Significance of 'Nuremberg' for Peace in the Nuclear Age". Nuremberg, 1985 November 23-1985 November 24; Typescript, materials (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 9)
    - "The True Topic of the Nuremberg Trials was the Future of Mankind". United Nations, 1986 September 27; Typescript, conference materials (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 10)
    - "The True Purpose of the Nuremberg Trials: To Save Mankind from the Scourge of War". Moscow, 1986 November 11-1986 November 13; Typescript, conference materials (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 11)
    - "The Significance of 'Nuremberg' for Peace". Panel discussion, UNESCO, Paris, 1986 December 13; Typescript (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 12)
    - "The Continuing Significance of the Judgments of the American Nuremberg Tribunals". Ann Arbor, MI, 1987 April 04; Typescript (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 13)
    - Introduction to the Panel. Conference on Nuclear Weapons and International Law, New York, 1987 August 29-1987 August 31; Typescript, conference materials (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 14)
    - "Der Entwurf eines Kodex der Verbrechen gegen den Frieden und die Sicherheit der Menschheit". East Berlin, 1987 September 28; Typescript, clippings, materials (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 15)
    - "Das Nuremberger Juristenurteil im Zeichen des 40. Jahrestages des Nuremberger Prozesses". East Berlin, 1987 September 28; Typescript, clippings (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 16)
    - "Die Bedeutung der Nurembergische Prinzipien fuer das Nuklearzeitalter". Potsdam, 1987 September 30; Typescript (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 17)
    - "The Lessons of the Nuremberg Tribunals for Securing Peace in Our Time". Humboldt University, 1987 October 02; Notes (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 18)
    - "The United Nations' Effort to Establish a Right of the Peoples to Peace". Moscow, 1989 June; Synopsis, conference materials (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 19)
    - "The Nazi Doctors and the Nuremberg Code of Medical Ethics". Boston, 1989 December 04-1989 December 05; Typescript, notes, conference materials (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 20)
    - "The Nazi Doctors and the Nuremberg Code of Medical Ethics". Materials, Undated (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 21)
    - Fried testimonial speech, 1989 December 14; Typescript (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 22)
  - Conferences, 1944-1990; 10.3; 52 file folders
    This sub-series contains conference materials, programs and correspondence relating to conferences attended by John Fried.
    - Conference on Germany After the War. New York, 1944 April 29-1944 April 30; 1944 June 03-1944 June 04; Program (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 23)
    - International Law Association, New York University Conference, 1958; Conference bulletin (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 24)
    - A.A.U.N., Manhattan Chapter Conference, 1960 December 03; Program (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 25)
    - "A Day at the United Nations". New York, 1961 February 25; Program (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 26)
    - 1961 Mid-Atlantic Model General Assembly. New York, 1961 March 24-1961 March 26; Program (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 27)
    - National Student Leadership Institute on the United Nations, Sarah Lawrence College, 1963 June 14-1963 June 21; Program, correspondence (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 28)
    - Conference on "The Evolution of Statecraft for International Co-operation and the Solution of Conflicts". 1964. Correspondence, Undated (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 29)
    - Conference of Scientists on Survival, University of Denver, 1964 June 19-1964 June 21; Program, correspondence (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 30)
    - National Lawyers Guild Twenty-Ninth Convention, New York City, 1967 February 10-1967 February 13; Program, correspondence (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 31)
    - Conference on "Military Conscription in the United States". Commission on Social Action of Reform Judaism, New York City, 1967 April 16; Correspondence (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 32)
    - Stockholm Conferences on Vietnam, July 6-9, 1967-1970, Undated; Conference materials (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 33)
    - "The United States in a Revolutionary World". Princeton University, 1968 April 02-1968 April 04; Program (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 34)
      Program.
    - United Nations Institute for Training and Research (UNITAR). Meeting, 1968 December 13 (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 35)
      List of panelists.
    - "The Nuremberg Trials and Objection to Military Service in Vietnam". American Society of International Law, 1969 April 24-1969 April 26; Programs, conference materials (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 36)
    - Fifth International Congress for Military Law and Law of War, Dublin, 1970 May 25-1970 May 30; Program, conference materials (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 37)
    - Stockholm Conference on Vietnam. Copenhagen, 1972 October 10-1972 October 16; Conference materials (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 38)
    - International Conference for the Implementation of the Paris Agreement, Stockholm, 1974 March 29-1974 March 31; Correspondece, materials (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 39)
    - Legal Conference on the Implementation of the Paris Agreement, Washington, DC, 1974 June 01-1974 June 02; Correspondence (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 40)
    - International Commission of Enquiry into Crimes of the Military Junta in Chile, Denmark, 1974 June 26-1974 June 27 (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 41)
      Draft of a resolution.
    - Conference on Security and Cooperation in Europe. Helsinki, 1975; Correspondece, materials (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 42)
    - Conference on the Nürnberg War Crimes Trials as History, Law and Morality, Washington, D.C., 1975 March 13-1975 March 14; Program, notes (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 43)
    - International Commission of Enquiry on Chile. Madrid, 1975 November; Notes (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 44)
    - 4th International Criminal Law Conference, San Juan, 1976 January; Correspondence, conference materials (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 45)
    - International Commission of Enquiry into the Crimes of the Military Junta in Chile, Stockholm, 1976 September 11; Conference materials (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 46)
    - International Human Rights Conference, Dedham, MA, 1976 October 21-1976 October 24; Program (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 47)
    - 2nd Philadelphia Conference on the Holocaust, 1977 February 16-1977 February 18; Program booklet (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 48)
    - Conference on the Holocaust, 1977 March 08; Program, correspondence (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 49)
    - Bridgetown, Barbados conference, 1977 May 27-1977 May 31; Notes, conference materials (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 50)
    - American Society of International Law, Washington, D.C., 1978 April 27-1978 April 29; Program, notes (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 51)
    - Conference on Micronesia, National Council of Churches, New York City, 1978 October 05; Correspondence (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 52)
    - World Conference in Solidarity with Chile, Madrid, 1978 November 09-1978 November 12; Correspondence (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 53)
    - International Association of Democratic Lawyers, Mission to Vietnam, 1979 April 25-1979 May 05; Notes (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 54)
      Itinerary.
    - Nuremberg reunion dinner, Washington, D.C., 1979 November 10; Program (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 55)
      Nuremberg directory.
    - International Studies Association, Los Angeles, CA, 1980 March 21; Conference materials, correspondence (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 56)
    - Columbia University Seminar on Problems of Peace, 1981 February 17; Program (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 57)
    - The Ninth General Conference of the International Peace Research Association, Orillia, Ottowa, 1981 June 21-1981 June 26; Conference program (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 58)
    - DBI/NGO Conference on Energy, 1981 September 10; Correspondence (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 59)
      Report on conference.
    - United States Military Academy Symposium on The Theory and Practice of American National Security 1945-1960, 1982 April 21-1982 April 23; Conference materials (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 60)
    - Mission dans les Territoires Occupés par Israël, 1982 May 22-1982 May 28; Conference materials (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 61)
    - International Symposium on Morality & Legality of Nuclear Weapons, New York City, 1982 June 04-1982 June 05; Correspondence, conference materials (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 62)
    - Annual Conference of the Dept. of Public Information for NGOs, 1982 September 08-1982 September 10 (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 63)
      Final report.
    - U.S. Anti-war delegation to Moscow, 1982 November 23-1982 December 02 (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 64)
    - "The Genetic Code of the Arms Race". Hunter College, 1983 April 12; Correspondence (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 65)
    - "The Nuclear Debate: Rationality, Morality, Security and Stability". United States Military Academy, Senior Conference XXI, West Point, NY, 1983 June 02-1983 June 04; Conference materials (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 66)
    - Second Annual Conference on Language and Communication, New York, 1983 December 15; Program (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 67)
    - Disarmament Forum, United Nations, New York, 1984 October 24-1984 October 30 (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 68)
    - CUNY Conference on European Peace Movement, 1984 December 07; Notes (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 69)
    - "Search and prosecution of Nazi criminals". Socialist Scholars Conference, CUNY, 1985 April 05-1985 April 06; Notes (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 70)
    - Facing History and Ourselves Conference, 1985; Correspondence, conference materials (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 71)
    - International Conference of Lawyers on 'The Rights of Peoples and International Cooperation as Prerequisites of Human Rights', Brussels, 1988 May 07-1988 May 08 (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 72)
      Conference proceedings.
    - International Symposium on the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child in Education, New York, 1989 June 15 (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 73)
      Conference outline.
    - 13th Congress of the International Association of Democratic Lawyers, Barcelona, 1990 March 20-1990 March 24; Program (Box 17 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 74)
  - Time Magazine/Fortune, 1943-1944; 10.4; 6 file folders
    This sub-series contains short reports written by Fried for Time Magazine/Fortune, international news cables, correspondence, and the text of an article on the International Labour Office published by Fortune.
    - Time Magazine/Fortune. Correspondence, 1943-1944 (Box 18 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 1)
    - Time Magazine/Fortune. Reports by John Fried, 1944 (Box 18 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 2)
    - "Report on Prisoner of War Camps", 1944 April 17 (Box 18 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 3)
    - International press releases, cables, 1943-1944 (Box 18 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 4)
    - "The International Labour Office". Correspondence with Fortune Magazine, 1944 (Box 18 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 5)
    - "The International Labour Office". Copy of article in Fortune, typescripts, 1944 (Box 18 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 6)
  - International Labour Office, Montreal, Canada, 1942-1954; 10.5; 8 file folders
    This series contains correspondence and reports prepared by Fried during and after his tenure at the International Labour Office in Montreal, Canada. Included in this series are the manuscript, background materials, and reviews of Fried's Exploitation of Foreign Labour by Germany, published in 1945 by the International Labour Office.
    - International Labour Office, Montreal, Canada. Correspondence and documents, 1942-1946 (Box 18 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 7)
    - International Labour Office. Correspondence, 1944-1954 (Box 18 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 8)
    - Reports authored by John Fried, 1944-1948 (Box 18 (10-Writings of John H. E. Fried), Folder 9)